Clow is an incredibly intuitive design tool that allowed me to move the design of my spring-summer
collection forward in the most incredible way.
It enabled me to take the roughest of sketches and, through pattern drafting in 2D, really
explore the shapes and fits that I wanted to make.
A truly revolutionary stage for me was taking these flat garment shapes and being able to
digitally sew and drape them into a 3D rendering.
Within minutes you can see a 3D image of what you're designing and make alterations on those
small decisions that make a design special.
Also being able to look at the same garment simulated in different materials and different
patterns.
Then seeing how those choices alter the drape and look and spirit of a garment was truly
revolutionary.
A truly revolutionary stage for me was taking these flat garment shapes and being able to
digitally sew and drape them into a 3D rendering.
Also being able to look at the shapes and patterns of the fabric, be able to consider the
details, and really create a 3D style to then be able to create something that I want to
make out of it.
I was able to do this with the help of my friend at the
Sunlight Studio.
Up next...
Thank you for watching.